{
    "id": "999ddeace2514338b92eb874db12a36c",
    "title": "Simple Present Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ………………….. playing cricket.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "enjoy",
                "enjoys",
                "enjoying"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3b2a07507ef7407b8d384d3c5077d661"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………………….. to wear expensive dresses.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "likes",
                "is liking"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "df3bdc566b2847e88c46525da448dd00"
        },
        {
            "question": "My sister ………………….. in Chennai.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "live",
                "lives",
                "am living"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c6ee082378244a2f9dc5df8fdc7e0f04"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………………… the right person for this job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "680ea84871f64fc78f9db42913a17b5b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where ………………………. you live?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "does",
                "do",
                "is"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3aac181127064beebd11728af183dce4"
        },
        {
            "question": "My brother ………………………. in the army.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "serve",
                "serves"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f17aeb14a50040c99c9d966eb57d13fc"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………………… the answer, but she won’t tell me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "know",
                "knows",
                "knowing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ca6d6974f5cc4ed68ea537d2330de96a"
        },
        {
            "question": "If I …………………… the answer, I will tell you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "know",
                "knows",
                "knowing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9092c1fb3bfe4752bbfc0652b349a983"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… the books on that table.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Put",
                "Puts",
                "Putting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d38d4990917d4ce88a139812e57446b9"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………………… French.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "know",
                "knows",
                "knowing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5130e495439640c0842ecad7cd08bc03"
        }
    ]
}